HOWIE NGUYEN

Riverside, CA 92507 | 5132825266 | hnguy431@ucr.edu

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

https://howie-portfolio.vercel.app/

Professional Summary

Dedicated Associate with extensive experience collaborating with clients, promptly identifying needs and recommending products and services to accomplish clients' goals. Strong communicator focused on delivering outstanding customer care.

Skills

- Attention to Detail
- Communication

- Collateral Management
- Warm and Friendly

Work History

Barn Associate Sep 2021 - Jul 2023

University Of California, Riverside

Riverside, CA

- Assisted with opening and closing procedures, ensuring the premises were ready for business and secure
 after hours.
- Kept dining and kitchen areas clean and organized, maintaining a comfortable environment for customers.
- Served customers in a friendly and efficient manner to ensure an excellent dining experience, leading to a 20% increase in repeat customers.
- Regularly checked on customers to refill drinks and respond to any requests, ensuring complete satisfaction.

Cashier Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Nordstrom Rack

San Diego, CA

- Greeted customers entering store and responded promptly to customer needs.
- Built relationships with customers to encourage repeat business.
- Operated cash register for cash, check, and credit card transactions with excellent accuracy levels.
- Helped customers complete purchases, locate items, and join reward programs.

Sales Associate Mar 2019 - Aug 2019

Hollister

Liberty Township, Ohio

- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers, and promote specific merchandise.
- Helped customers locate products and checked store system for merchandise at other sites.
- Managed returns, exchanges and refunds in accordance with store policy.
- Answered customer questions about sizing, accessories, and merchandise care.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

University of California Riverside

Jun 2023

Riverside, CA

Languages

Vietnamese

Limited Working